To be continued
This area is considered to be the
safest area for children in Japan.
But frequent patronese or working class
flu cases are high.
Hmm...
Thank you.
Please stand by.
Yes.
Fight, fight, I'll show you I can grab
it.
No matter how many times I fall, I
won't give up.
More, more, more, more.
Aiming for the top, I'll be a good boy.
I'm Junko.
I'm Fujii.
I'm Nagami.
Let's do our best!
I'm Karin.
I'm Yuna.
I'm Mimei.
I'm Kamiya.
I'm Wato.
We are Topp Topp!
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
Thank you.
We are the beautiful star cast of
Fujino.
We are Inori and Kusan.
Thank you.
We have a song that we want you to
listen to in Fukushima.
Please listen to it.
3000 Days.
Even after 3000 days,
this eyelid can only see your face.
You are the only one who can feel the
happiness.
I'm going to enjoy it so it's closed.
Are you all ready?
Yeah!
Let's go! Wonderful Tohoku!
I don't have a heart, I don't have a
heart
Translated by Releska
And the last song is our song!
Let's enjoy this song until the end!
Let's go!
We are Riinu! Let's go to the top!
See you!
Don't get heatstroke!
Thank you!
I'm pregnant.
It's good.
I like the taste of strawberry.
It's the wind of winter.
I'll sing tomorrow and come back to the
concert hall.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
I'm done.
It was hot.
It was great.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
I'm a gyaru.
Point shampoo.
I'm being photographed.
Stop it.
Take a picture of me.
Please stop it.
Thank you.
Look.
It's hot.
I'm enjoying it.
Ujiro.
Michinoko's Starbust.
Ikinari and Sainaki.
Thank you.
Thank you, Kyukyo.
Thank you very much.
I think it's a great opportunity to see
the fireworks with the people of
Mononofu.
I hope we can all share this happy time
together.
Let's enjoy it together!
I was watching the fireworks and I felt
proud of myself as a member of the same
club.
I thought that such a wonderful
fireworks would be held.
I was really happy to see it with such
wonderful people.
The stage of Haruichi Okoro seems to be
crying before the performance.
I was looking forward to the day.
I was really happy to share the
wonderful things with you.
I will never forget this day.
Thank you for your wonderful time.
We are a new club that is active mainly
in Tohoku.
Thank you for inviting us to the first
day of Haruichi Okoro.
The second day of Haruichi Okoro.
The third day of Haruichi Okoro.
The fourth day of Haruichi Okoro.
Let's go with that.
Karen!
Yuna!
San!
Shinju!
Noe!
Kaya!
Naka!
Rini!
Mura!
We are the Yami-no-San Club!
Let's have fun today!
Mura! Mura! Mura!
We are a lesson group that is active
mainly in Tohoku.
Thank you for coming to the second day
of the first day of the Momokuro Spring.
We will never be defeated!
We will never lose!
We will always, always,
be the best!
We will never be defeated!
We will always, always,
be the best!
We will never give up!
We will always, always,
be the best!
Let's go in a circle.
That's good!
Let's practice.
One, two, three!
Right circle?
Right circle!
Please!
Thank you!
I want to go to Stapler.
Isn't it difficult?
She is asking us where to eat highway-
style spreads
The contrast is amazing.
Go!
See you!
Don't stop!
It's my favorite color.
It's a member color.
Oh, yeah.
Wow!
Yeah!
Day 2.
I'm going to buy a manager.
I bought a bad guy.
I'm a bad guy.
It was fun to distribute the villa.
It was fun.
It's been a while since I've done it.
Yesterday, I was like,
Who is this?
Day 2,
I was like,
Everyone follows me when I jump in.
I wonder if you're watching.
If you got it, please join the fan
club.
Please watch YouTube.
I'm doing Instagram, too.
I can't see the number of people.
How was it yesterday and today?
There were more people today.
Yesterday,
I stopped for a while.
There were a lot of people going
somewhere.
This time, there were a lot of people
from the beginning.
You've been watching.
You've been watching me.
The first song is Sakura Promise.
Everyone's dancing.
I thought it was warm.
You're all so good.
I'm so proud of you.
You're so kind.
You're so blessed.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I'm grateful.
I'm here.
Thank you.